Would you look at that?
What a tasty morsel.
Now eat your fill.
Plus-Sized Elf
The Empress of the Park and the Demonic Dinner
Check out that lady, she's huge!
W-wow, no kidding...
Rawr! I'm gonna eat'cha!
They're so full of energy.
Staaaaaaaare.
The hell are you jerks starin' at?!
I've heard that female Ogres
have strong maternal instincts.
I guess that holds true
even for alcoholics like you.
Hold up! Th-this has nothing to do with me
liking kids, I just think they're cute and-
So, Ogres have a soft spot for kids, eh?
Oh shaddup!
Whoa there. Calm down.
Getting into a huff here will just make
all the kids laugh at you.
Huh?
Speaking of, where'd they all go?
Hey!
You're on my turf!
If you wanna pway awound here,
then you gotta pay up!
Omigod! How can something be this cute?!
Whuz the matter?
Stowp goofin' around and
fowk over da goods!
This brat doesn't know any manners.
Maybe I should come down on her
like a ton of bricks.
Oh, come on! It's normal for kids
to have a little sass!
Seeing you with such a goofy look
is kinda freaking me out.
This kid needs to learn how to
properly interact with her betters.
You down't get to wecture me! Bam! Bam!
Get your fat ass outta here, dumptwuck!
Bam! Bam! Bam!
Kuroeda?!
Bad girl.
Violence is a no-no.
Lemme go! How are you so stwong?!
So, your name is Kobo, huh?
That's MISS Kobo to you, bowl cut boy!
U-uh, okay.
Do you always extort people
when you're at the park?
It's my turf! So I can do whaddeva
I want to make a pwofit!
Wait, is that...?
The payments I cowwected fwom the kidz
who came to pway in the park.
SMIIIIIRK
But none of them couwd pay the extwa
for bawck taxes from befowe I came,
so I kicked them all outta here!
What a slumlord...
That's not nice.
Stealing from others is a no-no.
Why would you do that?
Well, the twuth is I got
abandoned by my pawents.
They weft me starving on the stweets,
so I did it to survive...
You know we can see the eyedrops.
Oh, you poor thing!
You believed that?!
It's okay! Let me take care of you!
I'll be your mommy now!
Lay off! You're bweaking my bones!
Fries 4 Life
There's no way in hell
someone starving for food
would have bulging curves
of flab on them like that.
How dare you!
I hate people talking abouwt my fwab!
Just wook at that ugwy sack of fat
you call a stomach!
I'm gonna smack the hell outta it!
Damn. She dodged.
What is she?
She's a Kobold sprite.
They have the physical appearance of kids,
but this is actually a full-grown adult.
Seriously?!
Elves, huh?
I shouwd've known fwom how slow you are.
And having that ugwy sack of fat
juwst makes you an even bigger slowpoke!
Elves aren't slowpokes!
Good wuck hitting me with those awwows!
Dammit! Quit scampering around!
C'mon! Whuz the matter?
You'll never hit me!
Butterballs like you couwd never hope
to pull off moves wike this!
Aw crap...
There's no escape for you now.
I can't bewieve this lard bucket of an Elf
got the bettew of me.
It's onwy cuz eating all the stupid candies
fwom the kidz made me fat.
They'd never beat me if I couwd
get bawck into shape!
Miss Kobo, would you like me to
teach you some facial exercises
to help improve your jawline?
Seriouswy?
But on one condition.
No more misbehaving.
Does that sound good?
All wight.
Lick
Making broad motions with
your mouth and tongue
will help to stimulate
the muscles in your face.
And despite differences in physique,
even people with smaller faces
can benefit from it.
Face lifting massages
are also very beneficial.
Here's how you do it. Just stretch like this.
So cute!
Make these part of your daily routine
and the contours of your face
will be sharper in no time!
I kept my end of the deal.
So please keep your promise, okay?
All wight.
A few days later...
Wh-what the?!
Oh, hey, Human.
Don't worry. After I did sowme dieting
and impwoved my wooks,
these kids gave me pwesents voluntarily.
Being popular makes life such a bweeze
it's awmost annoying.
Wow! She looks even more precious now!
Being popular makes life such a bweeze
it's awmost annoying.
I'm keeping my pwomise. No misbehaving.
Hewp me again the next time
I put on weight, okay?
Plus-Sized Elf
Plus-Sized Elf!
Massage Relaxation
You had French fries again, didn't you!
Um, well, they started selling
this limited-time flavor...
and I couldn't help myself.
Sounds like we need to ban you
from eating fries for a while.
Nuh-uh! Nuh-uh! Nuh-uh! Nuh-uh!
I can't live without fries!
Aw jeez, let go! You're freaking me out!
Squish
Squish?
Wait, this is...
a toxic waist!
No, we only say that about "waste"!
Is it just me or are you getting fat, Human?
I'll slim down!
I know that it's my responsibility as
your instructor to stay in good shape!
Tater Town
I'll start my mornings with
a cup of water.
Then have a well-balanced,
low-calorie breakfast
filled with fermented foods
and dietary fiber.
Add in a moderate amount of exercise
and my body should naturally
get back into proper shape.
I put on MORE weight?! But how?!
I must be cursed.
What's going to happen if I keep
putting on weight like this?
C'mon, Human. This mountain of
French fries is just for us.
Have as many as you want!
No, thanks. I'm on a diet-
Don't be shy!
Eat your fill.
Just a nightmare. Thank god.
Huh?
What the actual hell?!
Why am I eating all this?!
Oh? That's strange.
Nobody ever breaks free from my spell.
Anyways, just keeping eating
and satisfy your hunger.
It's all my home cooking.
Who are you?
And why are you in my house?
Don't pay any attention to me.
Stay focused on your meal.
Huh? I can't control my body...
Good boy. Eat up.
Say "ahhh".
Not so fast!
My magic got negated!
Are you okay, Human?
It's you two! What are you doing here?
We sensed very faint traces of a spell
that had been used on you.
So we secretly kept an eye on you
for any funny business!
What are filthy Elves doing here?
She's a Satyr!
They're a race of creatures who mainly feed
off the avarice that radiates from others.
Hunger
Delicious!
Radiates
Avarice
She used hypnosis magic to
forcibly provoke your appetite
and made you eat a bunch of food.
Then fed off the avarice that exuded off you.
It explains why you suddenly got fat.
Well, now that I'm here...
Now that I'M here,
you have nothing to worry about!
Hey! Don't steal my line,
you fat pig of an Elf!
Not my problem,
you inky-ass blubberbutt!
Wh-whatever!
Dinner time is when I get to make
practical use of my favorite hobby
and I won't let you ruin it!
"Hobby"?
Yes. My hobby is cooking.
The cuisine of this world
is rich with variety.
I have nothing but respect for how
voracious humans get with their food.
It's helped me to sharpen my cooking skills
while simultaneously indulging
in tasty avarice.
D-do you feed off people's
carnal desires, too?
No, get your lewd thoughts out of here!
Uh oh! The Human's getting beaten up!
We have to rescue him!
No can do.
All that fighting earlier strained my panties
to the point they'll snap if I even move.
Get away from the human,
you gluttonous Satyr bitch!
I'm putting a stop to your rampage!
Huh? You're the one who looks like
a glutton around here, fatty!
What?!
You're clearly leading a life of
indulgence with no self-control.
And that's no different from what I'm doing.
Enough talk!
Screw you and your slutty apron!
Ugh, I can't move!
This is what you get for
making fun of my outfit.
What the?!
Ha, ha. Just look at all that flab on you.
Damn you!
Now sit back and watch
as I fatten up the human.
My body's moving on its own!
Eat your fill.
Argh! Help me!
I can move again!
You handle the rest.
Good job, blubberbutt!
Take this!
Go figure.
Looks like you're a chubbo, too.
Except you got fat off avarice,
which is like air that nobody can see.
Doesn't that make you a balloon?
Watch out, Human!
No man has seen my naked body before!
You ruined my first time!
Seriously?
That's the end of that.
Her panties are torn apart...
No, it's not over yet.
Satyrs have a strong attachment
to their prey.
She'll be back again.
So, here's my idea!
After that, everyone started to
take turns protecting me.
Try this on for size!
You're still adorable,
even if you are an adult!
I love these chubby cheeks!
Lemme go! I'm owder than you!
What? You are?!
Wah! I lost to blubberbutt!
I wanna rematch!
You're never going to win.
It's a little rowdy, but now I can
continue my diet without worries.
I will have my revenge!